[music]
[музыка]
look yesterday the city of Kremenchug was hit hard by missiles
посмотрите вчера сильно ударило ракетами
on a merchant tank
по городу кременчуг по торговому танку
, 18 people have already died, more than 30 have gone
уже погибло 18 человек больше 30 пропали
missing, for that I speak the same for myself
без вести для того я для себя на этом же
and that 1000 people remember the
говорит и что 1000 человек помню
telegram channel watched what and in honor of the
телеграм-канал смотрел то что а в честь
question yes our relationship  don’t wait,
вопрос да наши отношения не подожди во
first of all, how can I die from a rocket in a
первых как от ракеты могу умереть в
shopping center in which there were 1000
торговом центре в который находился 1000
people 18, too, the rocket should
человек 18 тоже ракета должна вам всё
repent of everything, well, in fact, the
раскаялись ну на самом деле
fragmentation action was spent, what kind of
осколочное действие тратил еще какая
rocket flew by,
ракета пролетела
how do you feel about the fact that your country is
как вы относитесь к тому что ваша страна
shelling shopping centers
обстреле торговые центры
and what ticket shelling  it
да какой билет обстрел это находит мне
seems to me that questions are possible, but we
кажется вопросы можно но мы свою страну
love and respect our country in any case, that is,
любим и уважаем в любом случае то есть
even if it kills many people, our
даже если она убивает многие люди наше
fatherland, in any case, we will love
отечество в любом случае мы будем любить
and respect
и уважать
well, and the people who lived in Germany under
хорошо а люди которые германии жили при
Hitler when Hitler burned the Jews
гитлере когда гитлер сжигал евреям
alive, they are also just  they loved Germany
живьём они тоже просто любили германию
because it is their homeland,
из за того что это их родина
it’s different, and why we
это другой а почему на
just love Russia to Russia, but for some reason
просто любим россию но почему-то
deliver it  go you love her but she now
доставить его вы любите ее но она сейчас
she can't chat can say fret to his
она не чат может сказать лада своей
homeland without killing people
родине не убивая людей
first he immediately
первыми он сразу
russia and germany nazi [ __ ] you
россию с и германии нацистской [__] вы
lunges shy deify you hitler
выпады роблять обожествляет вы гитлер
you aliens you have this bald without your
вас пришельцы у вас этот лысый без вашей
help you can say yes i can just
помощью можно говори да я могу просто
show me  I can look at an
показать я могу смотрите на против
information war is being waged against Russia,
россии ведется информационная война и
and all this [ __ ] of boles, no matter the bomb, we
вот эта вся [__] штамбов бы ни бомбы мы
free the residents of Donbass who
освобождаем жителей донбасса которые
have been under oppression for eight years;
были восемь лет под гнетом это укрывает
and a
видел если просто он был тот и
pakistani someone by nationality,
пакистанец кто-то по национальности
to be honest, a
честно сказать
dutch without arms wo
голландец безруков не на серьезную нас
n’t separate us seriously and the poet’s head is a
не разлучит и башке у
multinational nato
поэта многонациональная нато
bashkortostan attestation [ __ ] yes bros
башкортостан аттестации [__] да братюни
miss polushki germans but who
мисс полушки немцы но то кто
will become us without a prompter at all i
станет нас еще без суфлера вообще я
can note 2 i’ll try on such a
могу note 2 я попробую на такой
little boy  the opachki didn’t help,
маленький мальчик не помогли опачки
look it turns out, let’s say the Ukrainians
смотри получается допустим украинцы то
didn’t capture the Donbass and the transfer, or
не захватывали донбасс и передачу или
for this you need to kill people in  shopping
для этого надо убивать людей в торговых
centers in the houses of the nine-story building is
центров в домах девятиэтажка
waiting for infection, let's topaz, I'll
дожидается заражу давай топаз буду
dishonor myself, let the prompter go for a
позорить сам давай суфлер уходит на
smoke break, after all, everything that is
перекур все-таки все что сейчас
happening now is all extremely ambiguous
происходит это все крайне неоднозначные
, after all, I think that there is still an
все таки я думаю что ведется все-таки
information war being waged, this is all fake, that
информационная война это все фэйки то
is, you consider a diluted
есть вы считаете фэйком разбавленный
shopping center to be a fake  boxes and why
торговый центр ящиков и а почему
is there an information war against
ведется информационная война против
russia
россии
russia is waging an information war against
россия ведет информационную войну против
ukraine
украины
it is not waging a war against ukraine it
она не ведёт войну против украины она
liberates against ukrainian don’t you
освобождает против украинской а вам не
think that news of taste is always the
кажется что всегда новости вкуса это и
information war of
есть информационная война россии
russia what is the question once again it seems to you that the
в чем вопрос еще раз вам на кажется что
junta is  just the information war of
хунта это как раз информационная война
Russia against Ukraine, this term is
россии против украины вот этот термин
not, this is exactly what has been happening
нет это именно что происходит происходил
in Ukraine since 2014, the fact that the authorities
на украины с 2014 года то что власть
took the pro-Western fascist capital,
взяли фашистский капитал прозападную
which is against Russia, the court all this is a
который против россии суд все это
dam, you will get
плотина вы
infected
заразитесь
lawyer ay-yay theorist and the program to hand over
юрист ай-яй theorist и программе сдавать
and you can see we’ll talk about what kind of fox  the main one is
и видно поговорим какие лисий основной
already on contests to i specially tova  r
уже на конкурсы к я специально товар
secondary vocational education
средние профессиональное образование
law and welfare
право и социальное обеспечение
medium this is a [ __ ]
средние это петух
this is college then I'm on purpose I'm just singing
это колледж то я специально я просто пою
here you mr college tell me
вот вы мистер колледж скажите
what is the legal basis for your
какие есть юридические основания у вашей
country
страны
to bomb my country
бомбить мою страну
liberate the
юридические основания освобождать
inhabitants of donbass from ukraine
жителей донбасса от украины
because they accepted their will swell
потому что они приняли свою волю зыбина
they don’t want to they accepted to say they
такое не хотят они приняли к сказать они
said no firmware when can you
сказали нет прошивка когда можете
tell the date when I said no mincemeat to a
сказать дату когда я сказала нет фарша
second and in what form, as it were, well, this is
секунде и в какой форме как бы ну это
an example of 2013 2014 not but so what does it mean
пример 2013 2014 не а вот так что значит
grandma had an effect on this, you didn’t go to
сказались бабушка к этого не выходили на
rallies, you say that
митинги говоришь ты что
someone went out, someone don’t go out
кто-то выходили кто-то не выходи
legally
юридически
don’t, well, you know a lot in Russia, a
не ну что значит много знаете в россии
lot of people went out to the swamp square and
много людей вышла на болотную площадь и
that,
что
well, in general, we do
ну в общем мы не либералов
n’t like liberals, don’t like liberals, are
не любите либерала до
also more cynical than bastards  so finally you
тоже циничнее [__] таки так ваще
can find pacifique c all the same, here in them is the
найти pacifique c все таки вот в них
film UAZ when the king of Thebes of the river is about to be
фильм уаз когда царь фив реки вот буде
cadi through oddities  butch put
кади через странностей буча ставьте
likes
лайки
kremenchug you sofiyka acute
кременчуг тебя софийке острых
haggle in sofiyka anything at the wheel
торговаться в софийке всякое на за рулем
she hid herself shelling in
она это [__] сами себя обстреле в
kramatorsk and everyone stole the composition of the river c at the station
краматорске попал и по вокзалу состав
.  and then the
реки c все украли . и тогда
bastards were given a loss
[__] а утрате им дали